arab-eye.com 2014-12-25

# Yahoo Privacy Center

## WHAT THIS PRIVACY AND COOKIE POLICY COVERS

This Privacy Policy covers Yahoo!'s treatment of personal information that Yahoo! collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Yahoo! products and services. Personal information includes information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

The Privacy Policy also gives information about cookies; Yahoo!'s and third parties' use of cookies; and how you may disable such cookies. 

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Yahoo! does not own or control, or to people that Yahoo! does not employ or manage. In addition, some companies that Yahoo! has acquired have their own, preexisting privacy policies which may be viewed on our acquired companies page.

This Privacy Policy incorporates, where applicable, any additional guidance about our privacy practices relating to particular products or services that can be found under the section "More about Yahoo! Privacy" on the top left of this page. 

"Yahoo!” means Yahoo! Inc. (based in the United States), except where the relevant service is provided by another Yahoo! group company, in which case references to Yahoo! shall, in respect of those services, be references to that Yahoo! Group company. Find out more information about Yahoo! data storage and data transfer.

Return to top

##  INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

Yahoo! collects personal information when you register for a Yahoo! account, when you use certain Yahoo! [products or services](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/products.html), when you enter [promotions or sweepstakes](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/promotions/) and when you visit Yahoo! pages or the pages of certain Yahoo! partners outside the branded Yahoo! network of websites. Yahoo! may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 

When you register with Yahoo!, we ask for your name, email address, birth date, gender, post code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with Yahoo! and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 

Yahoo! collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer.

Yahoo! also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your [IP address](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/xe/yahoo/ip), Yahoo! [cookie](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/xe/yahoo/cookies) information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you requested. 

Yahoo! uses information for the following general purposes: to personalize the advertising and content you see, based on the details given by you at registration and your activity at Yahoo!, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. You agree that Yahoo! may transfer your personal information for the general purposes set out above to any Yahoo! group company worldwide.

Return to top

## INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

Yahoo! does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Yahoo! under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Yahoo! communicate with you about offers from Yahoo! and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, legal process, or to any legitimate request by authorities with which we must comply. 
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Yahoo!'s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
  * This is within the Yahoo! group, for the purposes described under “Information Collection & Use” above (for example, various companies in the Yahoo! group are responsible for storing and processing your information in order to deliver content to you). 
  * Yahoo! may transfer information about you if Yahoo! acquires, or is acquired by or merged with, another company. In this event, Yahoo! will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

Yahoo! displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria—for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area. 

  * Yahoo! does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 
  * Yahoo! advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies). 

Yahoo! works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business. For more information regarding providers of products or services that you've requested please read our detailed [ reference links](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/all). 

Return to top

## COOKIES

Yahoo! may set and access Yahoo! cookies on your computer. 

Yahoo! allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Yahoo!'s cookies. 

Yahoo! uses web beacons to access our cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with Yahoo! products and services. 

To find out more about how we use cookies and how to disable cookies, click here.

Return to top

## YOUR ABILITY TO EDIT AND DELETE YOUR ACCOUNT INFORMATION AND PREFERENCES

You can edit your [ Yahoo Account Information](http://edit.yahoo.com/config/eval_profile), including your [ marketing preferences ](http://subscribe.yahoo.com/showaccount) at any time. You can also modify information you have provided to Yahoo through the Yahoo [products or services](https://io.help.yahoo.com/contact/index?page=contact&locale=en_JO&y=PROD_ACCT&token=w5FCchB1dWH7qK38juuR7x2It3svV1dhjhGb4jqs3W6AHCiLjm7SCFJmJZKi97QrPrNGzREPjHNmBuz5p9SSIQNFAUOpNhARa3CWEh6LH89Kao3hHdSG7SMXh16qBd2FQX1RyiGqOTk%3D#) you may use.

New categories of marketing communications might be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications, such as service announcements and administrative messages and other communications relating to the Yahoo! service, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. 

You may delete your Yahoo! account by visiting our [Account Deletion](https://edit.yahoo.com/config/delete_user) page, verifying your password once more and confirming your choice to terminate the account. Please click here to read about what information may possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted. 

Return to top

## CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with our legal obligations to protect personal information about you. 

To learn more about security, including the security steps we have taken and security steps you can take, please read  Security at Yahoo! 

Return to top

## POSTING ON PUBLICLY ACCESSIBLE AREAS

A publicly accessible area is any area of Yahoo! that is accessible by the general public and may be indexed by search engines.

Yahoo! offers you the opportunity to post, submit and exchange content and information on publicly accessible areas, such as Yahoo! Groups, Yahoo! Message Boards and Yahoo! Answers.

You should exercise caution if you choose to disclose personal information in a publicly accessible area. Remember that this information may remain indefinitely in the publicly accessible area of the Service. Also, depending on the particular Service, other users may also be able to view two or more of your individual postings collectively. 

You are solely responsible for any personal information that you disclose and disseminate on publicly accessible areas. 

If you have a concern about any personal information you have posted on any publicly accessible areas and are unable to delete or edit it, please refer your query to [Customer Care.](http://help.yahoo.com/help/xe/abuse)

Return to top

##  CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Yahoo! may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Yahoo! account or by posting a prominent notice on our pages. 

Return to top

## QUESTIONS OR SUGGESTIONS

If you have questions or suggestions complete a [feedback form](https://io.help.yahoo.com/contact/index?y=PROD_ACCT&token=w5FCchB1dWFBK0e02%252BwEylJn1ziDqePb2Dq22Z0PBKmuG9cZpE4MM9vS6l0r8gi9F6k%252FK8nik5MH8JQjZy5NlWIyygEGVpVVsSm9NHim7CEyQill6QA5So4LitBJKzIR70TrNbvHb%252Bs%253D&locale=en_JO&page=contactform&selectedChannel=email-icon). 

Last updated: August 14, 2010

Return to top

## CHILDREN

With parental permission, a child under age 13 might have a Yahoo Family Account. Visit [Children's Privacy & Family Accounts](https://info.yahoo.com/privacy/xe/yahoo/family/details.html) to learn more about children’s privacy on Yahoo.

Return to top
